Guide to the Cornell United Religious Work records, 1869-1972,
Cornell United Religious Work records
- Series I
  - Foreign students, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Religious background of foreign students, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Freshman discussion groups, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Freshman commission, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Freshman area, 1956-1960 (Box 35, Folder 44-45)
  - Community development board (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Inter-office, 1962-1963 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Committees, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Curriculum evaluation workshop, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Religious Education Association, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - University Christian Mission, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - International Studies Project, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Danforth Foundation report, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Service projects: Latin America, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Inventory: annual lists and non-current pertinent papers, Anabel Taylor floor plans, 1957-1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Info regarding One World room murals: buildings and equiptment, 1952-1953 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Working folder for 5-74 inventory, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Former furnishings, Barnes Hall (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Information on electronic organs: building and equipment, 1951-1957 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Commons coffeehouse and Spring Day clippings (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Memorial lobby Anabel Taylor list, 1941-1945 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Faculty opinion questionnaires (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation committee: Myron Bloy correspondence and report (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Faculty opinion questionnaire first draft, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation: Transcription of morning report, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Report: Committee on Evaluation, presented to CURW board, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - United Ministry at Cornell University, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - CURW annual board meeting, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Student opinion questionnaires, completed and extra copies, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Political turmoil, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Criteria and evaluations, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, clippings, notes, 1960s-1980 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Resource materials, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Name labels and stationary (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Board and staff materials, 1975-1980 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam and Civil Rights clippings, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Reports, drafts (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Board files, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - CURW annual reports, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Current Cornell schedule, materials, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Wedding information and photograph of Jewish wedding chuppah (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - OARC and maps (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - CRESP information, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Cornell facilities, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Cornell transportation and parking, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Anabel Taylor Hall papers and clippings, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - United Way, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Telephone materials, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Anabel Taylor Hall: Use of kitchen, physical plant, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 37-38)
  - General correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Board of Control program committee, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Program Committee minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee on the board, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee CURW minutes, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - CURW board minutes, papers, 1961-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5-8)
  - Nominations to board, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - CURW board meeting minutes, papers, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 10-14)
  - CURW board minutes, papers, 1970, 1977-1980 (Box 37, Folder 15-19)
  - CURW board minutes, papers, 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 20-22)
  - Posters and fliers for concerts and sermons, 1980s-1990s (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Poster for The Other America II, featuring Mitchell S. Jackson, 2018-01-23 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Sage Chapel Programs, Bulletins, and Sermons
    - Sage Chapel Sermons, 1960s-2000s (Box 30)
      Program or transcript of speeches given.
    - Sage Chapel bulletins, 1950-1987 (Box 31)
      Programs for services, performances, concerts, and other events at Sage Chapel.
    - Sage Chapel bulletins, 1987-2000 (Box 32)
  - Annual Report of the Director, 1971-1987 (Box 32)
  - Student Manual, Handbook, Source Book, 1948-1964 (Box 32)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1267 - 1)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1268 - 1)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1268 - 2)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1268 - 3)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 1)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 2)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 3)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 4)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 5)
  - Unprocessed (Box 39-2-1604 - 6)